

Karen Simonyan

Full Stack Developer

I have been working with web development since 2014, the period during which I have worked in different environments, from big consultancy companies to start-ups. I am a self-motivated and self-taught professional who likes to solve problems. I merge a passion for usability and user experience with technical knowledge to create cool digital experiences. My repertoire includes programming languages and tools such as Angular, Vue.JS, Node.js, ReactJS, EmberJS, Mobx, Wordpress, PHP (Laravel, Codeigniter, Symfony, Zend, MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Nginx and Apache server configuration, Gulp, SASS, LESS, Twitter Bootstrap, Susy, jQuery, and more.

developerkarensimonyan@gmail.com

Yerevan, Armenian

devkaren.github.io/

+374 77 49 79 70

20 June, 1996

in linkedin.com/in/developerkarensimonyan

LANGUAGES

English

Russian

Professional Working Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

SKILLS

WordPress

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Developer

08/2021 - 11/2021

Front End Team Lead

ArmBoldMind

01/2021 - 07/2021

Freelance Developer

06/2020 - 12/2020

Senior Full-Stack Developer ECRO

01/2020 - 06/2020

Senior Full-Stack Developer

ERASOFTS 04/2017 - 01/2020

Full-Stack Developer

SOFTCODE

09/2015 - 03/2017

EDUCATION

BA (bachelor's degree) IT security NATIONAL POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY OF ARMENIA

2011 - 2015

Science and Mathematics

High School

2009 - 2011

PERSONALITY

Perseverance Open-minded

Punctual

Hard-working

Result-oriented

Highly inquisitive